Writing a hundred test cases by hand
takes weeks.
Watch this AI do it
in thirty seconds.
Manual test writing is slow,
error-prone, and doesn't scale.
This dashboard changes everything.
Point this AI at any web app.
It explores every page,
discovers user flows,
and maps API endpoints —
completely on its own.
No scripts, no setup —
just a URL.
From exploration to production-ready
Playwright tests — fully automated.
Requirements extraction,
test generation,
and self-healing validation —
all in one pipeline.
When a test breaks,
the AI fixes it automatically.
Not just UI tests.
API testing from OpenAPI specs.
Load testing with real-time metrics.
Multi-tier security scanning.
Database quality checks.
Even LLM evaluation
for your AI models.
CI/CD integration
with GitHub and GitLab.
Full requirements traceability.
Regression reports.
Cron scheduling.
Multi-project isolation.
AI-powered test automation.
From zero to full coverage.
Try it today.